[
  {
    "name": "AdditionTutorial",
    "type": "AdditionTutorialState",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [
        {
          "name": "ArithmeticHandler",
          "params": {
            "problem": "1+2=",
            "solution": 3
          }
        },
        {
          "name": "TotalTime"
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeState",
    "name": "AdditionPractice",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—8=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-6=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }]
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeFinishedState_return",
    "desc_head": "SymbolicNumberComparison_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "SymbolicNumberComparison_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [ { "name": "TaskHandler", "params": { "num_left": "1", "num_right": "2", "solution": 2, "distance": 1 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ] ] },
  {
    "type": "ArithmeticState",
    "name": "Addition",
    "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+3=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+4=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+5=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+6=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+7=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+8=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+9=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+2=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+4=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+5=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+6=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+7=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+8=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+9=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+2=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+3=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+5=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+6=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+7=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+8=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+9=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+2=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+3=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+4=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+6=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+7=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+8=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+9=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+2=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+3=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+4=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+5=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+7=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+8=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+9=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+2=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+3=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+4=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+5=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+6=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+8=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+9=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+2=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+3=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+4=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+5=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+6=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+7=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+9=", "solution": 17 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+2=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+3=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+4=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+5=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+6=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+7=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+8=", "solution": 17 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],

      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+3=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+4=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+5=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+6=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+7=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+8=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2+9=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+2=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+4=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+5=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+6=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+7=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+8=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3+9=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+2=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+3=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+5=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+6=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+7=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+8=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4+9=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+2=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+3=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+4=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+6=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+7=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+8=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5+9=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+2=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+3=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+4=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+5=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+7=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+8=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6+9=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+2=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+3=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+4=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+5=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+6=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+8=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7+9=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+2=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+3=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+4=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+5=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+6=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+7=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8+9=", "solution": 17 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+2=", "solution": 11 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+3=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+4=", "solution": 13 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+5=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+6=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+7=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],
      [ { "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9+8=", "solution": 17 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ],

      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10+12+34=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "49+12+70=", "solution": 131 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "82+32+78=", "solution": 192 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74+72+50=", "solution": 196 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94+88+34=", "solution": 216 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68+57+57=", "solution": 182 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12+64+46=", "solution": 122 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "71+11+97=", "solution": 179 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "28+62+46=", "solution": 136 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81+27+80=", "solution": 188 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "54+35+30=", "solution": 119 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "98+74+99=", "solution": 271 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "95+92+53=", "solution": 240 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13+85+15=", "solution": 113 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "89+42+38=", "solution": 169 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "71+46+96=", "solution": 213 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "58+13+82=", "solution": 153 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55+51+28=", "solution": 134 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55+33+37=", "solution": 125 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "49+99+26=", "solution": 174 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "75+17+92=", "solution": 184 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46+65+73=", "solution": 184 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68+52+20=", "solution": 140 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13+19+26=", "solution": 58 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "50+10+16=", "solution": 76 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13+23+95=", "solution": 131 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12+76+92=", "solution": 180 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23+26+25=", "solution": 74 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40+59+21=", "solution": 120 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "44+45+39=", "solution": 128 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "31+56+21=", "solution": 108 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99+39+31=", "solution": 169 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "88+43+84=", "solution": 215 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "79+41+36=", "solution": 156 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "88+28+43=", "solution": 159 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40+66+77=", "solution": 183 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "67+83+57=", "solution": 207 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "63+26+17=", "solution": 106 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19+86+60=", "solution": 165 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76+30+30=", "solution": 136 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97+38+46=", "solution": 181 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68+39+17=", "solution": 124 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "98+57+57=", "solution": 212 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "34+21+92=", "solution": 147 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "59+59+95=", "solution": 213 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "33+38+18=", "solution": 89 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "80+95+76=", "solution": 251 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "37+40+86=", "solution": 163 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78+31+25=", "solution": 134 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97+52+12=", "solution": 161 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "56+56+29=", "solution": 141 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "65+23+28=", "solution": 116 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15+95+51=", "solution": 161 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "41+62+35=", "solution": 138 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73+74+60=", "solution": 207 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68+99+97=", "solution": 264 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84+73+66=", "solution": 223 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97+11+58=", "solution": 166 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68+15+98=", "solution": 181 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "89+56+96=", "solution": 241 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],

     

[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5-3=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6-4=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-5=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-6=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-7=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-8=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-9=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5-2=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-4=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-5=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-6=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-7=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-8=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-9=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6-2=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-3=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-5=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-6=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-7=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-8=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-9=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-2=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-3=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-4=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-6=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-7=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-8=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-9=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-2=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-3=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-4=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-5=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-7=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-8=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-9=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-2=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-3=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-4=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-5=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-6=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-8=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16-9=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-2=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-3=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-4=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-5=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-6=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-7=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17-9=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-2=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-3=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-4=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-5=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-6=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16-7=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17-8=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],

[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5-3=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6-4=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-5=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-6=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-7=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-8=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-9=", "solution": 2 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5-2=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-4=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-5=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-6=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-7=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-8=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-9=", "solution": 3 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6-2=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-3=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-5=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-6=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-7=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-8=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-9=", "solution": 4 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7-2=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-3=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-4=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-6=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-7=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-8=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-9=", "solution": 5 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8-2=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-3=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-4=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-5=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-7=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-8=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-9=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9-2=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-3=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-4=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-5=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-6=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-8=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16-9=", "solution": 7 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10-2=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-3=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-4=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-5=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-6=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-7=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17-9=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11-2=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12-3=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13-4=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14-5=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15-6=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16-7=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17-8=", "solution": 9 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],

[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92-13=", "solution": 79 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94-25=", "solution": 69 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83-15=", "solution": 68 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84-49=", "solution": 35 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "67-38=", "solution": 29 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51-13=", "solution": 38 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-16=", "solution": 57 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-24=", "solution": 49 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "86-49=", "solution": 37 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74-38=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81-17=", "solution": 64 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "61-46=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83-46=", "solution": 37 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91-15=", "solution": 76 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51-27=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-37=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "93-29=", "solution": 64 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "82-47=", "solution": 35 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "56-19=", "solution": 37 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85-26=", "solution": 59 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91-68=", "solution": 23 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "62-38=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92-14=", "solution": 78 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97-49=", "solution": 48 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "71-53=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83-48=", "solution": 35 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "95-17=", "solution": 78 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "71-34=", "solution": 37 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83-37=", "solution": 46 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92-67=", "solution": 25 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "61-37=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "82-45=", "solution": 37 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "72-25=", "solution": 47 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-15=", "solution": 58 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "61-32=", "solution": 29 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85-58=", "solution": 27 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83-18=", "solution": 65 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "93-34=", "solution": 59 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81-56=", "solution": 25 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "41-17=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "63-48=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76-17=", "solution": 59 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76-19=", "solution": 57 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "53-17=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81-23=", "solution": 58 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74-25=", "solution": 49 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "93-47=", "solution": 46 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "42-27=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91-62=", "solution": 29 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "41-26=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85-29=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97-69=", "solution": 28 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91-23=", "solution": 68 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84-56=", "solution": 28 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-56=", "solution": 17 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "82-64=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97-19=", "solution": 78 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73-17=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92-64=", "solution": 28 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92-38=", "solution": 54 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],

[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—3=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—4=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—5=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—6=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—7=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—8=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2Ã—9=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—2=", "solution": 6 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—4=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—5=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—6=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—7=", "solution": 21 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—8=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3Ã—9=", "solution": 27 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—2=", "solution": 8 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—3=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—5=", "solution": 20 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—6=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—7=", "solution": 28 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—8=", "solution": 32 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4Ã—9=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—2=", "solution": 10 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—3=", "solution": 15 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—4=", "solution": 20 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—6=", "solution": 30 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—7=", "solution": 35 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—8=", "solution": 40 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5Ã—9=", "solution": 45 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—2=", "solution": 12 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—3=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—4=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—5=", "solution": 30 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—7=", "solution": 42 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—8=", "solution": 48 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6Ã—9=", "solution": 54 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—2=", "solution": 14 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—3=", "solution": 21 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—4=", "solution": 28 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—5=", "solution": 35 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—6=", "solution": 42 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—8=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7Ã—9=", "solution": 63 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—2=", "solution": 16 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—3=", "solution": 24 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—4=", "solution": 32 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—5=", "solution": 40 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—6=", "solution": 48 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—7=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8Ã—9=", "solution": 72 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—2=", "solution": 18 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—3=", "solution": 27 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—4=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—5=", "solution": 45 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—6=", "solution": 54 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—7=", "solution": 63 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9Ã—8=", "solution": 72 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],

[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—3=", "solution": 36 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—4=", "solution": 48 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—5=", "solution": 60 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—6=", "solution": 72 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—7=", "solution": 84 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12Ã—8=", "solution": 96 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13Ã—3=", "solution": 39 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13Ã—4=", "solution": 52 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13Ã—5=", "solution": 65 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13Ã—6=", "solution": 78 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13Ã—7=", "solution": 91 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14Ã—3=", "solution": 42 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14Ã—4=", "solution": 56 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14Ã—5=", "solution": 70 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14Ã—6=", "solution": 84 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14Ã—7=", "solution": 98 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15Ã—3=", "solution": 45 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15Ã—4=", "solution": 60 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15Ã—5=", "solution": 75 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15Ã—6=", "solution": 90 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16Ã—3=", "solution": 48 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16Ã—4=", "solution": 64 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16Ã—5=", "solution": 80 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16Ã—6=", "solution": 96 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17Ã—3=", "solution": 51 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17Ã—4=", "solution": 68 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17Ã—5=", "solution": 85 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "18Ã—3=", "solution": 54 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "18Ã—4=", "solution": 72 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "18Ã—5=", "solution": 90 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19Ã—3=", "solution": 57 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19Ã—4=", "solution": 76 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19Ã—5=", "solution": 95 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20Ã—3=", "solution": 60 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20Ã—4=", "solution": 80 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "21Ã—3=", "solution": 63 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "21Ã—4=", "solution": 84 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22Ã—3=", "solution": 66 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22Ã—4=", "solution": 88 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23Ã—3=", "solution": 69 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23Ã—4=", "solution": 92 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24Ã—3=", "solution": 72 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24Ã—4=", "solution": 96 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "25Ã—3=", "solution": 75 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "26Ã—3=", "solution": 78 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "27Ã—3=", "solution": 81 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "28Ã—3=", "solution": 84 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "29Ã—3=", "solution": 87 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "30Ã—3=", "solution": 90 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "31Ã—3=", "solution": 93 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "32Ã—3=", "solution": 96 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
[{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "33Ã—3=", "solution": 99 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" }]

    ] }, 
    { "name": "TaskDoneState", "type": "TaskDoneState", "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD", "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY", "done": false, "saved": false, "trials": [ ] }, 
    { "type": "SAVE", "done": false, "saved": false }, { "type": "REDIRECT", "done": false, "saved": false,
    "to": { "type": "GotoNextState" } } ]